(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
All characters, behaviours, settings, and events depicted in this drama are entirely fictitious.
They are not designed to allude to any particular entity, occupation, or group of people.
Viewer discretion is advised.
[North Star Entertainment]
♫I never know what love is like♫
♫All my life, never once have I experienced it♫
♫No one to take that place in my heart♫
♫But now that I’ve met you, my heart begins to glow♫
♫What feeling is this? Why is my heart fluttering?♫
♫And I just can’t control it.♫
♫What happened to my heart right now?♫
♫I can’t control it when you’re around♫
♫This heart…it stops at you♫
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
[Waves of Deception]
[Previously]
[Nate]: Do you swear it’s only about work?
Isn’t it because you’ve already fallen into your own trap?
[Lada]: I chose this one.
Isn’t too simple?
[Lada]: That’s why it’s interesting.
[Adisorn]: If one day, you ever meet someone…
who can make your heart flutter,
that person is someone you should cherish for life.
I’m going to make you say it out loud that I’m good at my job.
I’ll be waiting.
[Lada]: You want me to…
[Pheempat]: Sabotage Chef Ian’s food.
And blame it all on the Watin Group.
If it were you,
will you choose being right or being preferred?
Being right.
[Lada]: But sometimes, being preferred is important too.
All done, Miss.
Thank you.
It’s time, Boss.
Today will be the best day for all of us.
Hello, everyone. I’m Apo Watinwanich,
Executive President of Monarch Global International Hotel.
As you might already know, recently the Watin Group has had the honour to welcome a famous chef…
renowned not only among our country but also across Asia.
And I believe she will soon earn herself an international title as a world-class chef.
Without further ado, please give it up and welcome Chef Ian.
This is Chef Ian.
She’ll be working with us to create a signature menu for the Watin Group.
Please get ready, Chef.
I believe you all must be wondering now what the Watin Group’s signature is.
I’m sure everyone will find it surprising once I say it…
because it sounds very plain and simple.
But every day of our life, we already have a lot to worry about.
So, when it comes to eating, we wouldn’t want to spend much time thinking about it.
Are you getting sick of asking yourself this question–“What should I eat for dinner?”
I chose this one.
Isn’t it too simple?
Because it’s simple, that’s why it’s interesting.
Everyday, we already have to go through a busy and hectic life all day long.
Then, we still have to think about what to have for dinner.
Why don’t we try something simple and not complicated?
Make an ordinary thing special.
Make a lasting impression for our guests, so that they’d want to come back.
That’s my idea.
Please go ahead with your creation.
I’m going home, sweetie.
Please take good care of yourself, Lada.
Work hard.
And don’t let Pat down, okay?
Yes, Mum.
- It’s done.
- Okay.
This menu is Seafood Bucket.
But we’ve given it a special name called ’’The Lively Sea”.
Such a plain menu yet flavourful and simply delicious.
If you want to try it, you must come to our hotel only.
In a minute, our staff will be serving this special dish to all of you.
Why are you hiding when the best part is about to come?
Boss, why are you here?
It’s me who should ask you that.
What’s a foodie girl like you doing out here…
when the guests are trying out our new menu?
Here, try it.
You brought it for me?
Are you all right?
Yes.
Don’t you want to try it?
Maybe later.
I still have to go help Miss Preem inside.
Please excuse me then.
Is the sea tired? Why isn’t it cheerful?
Yes?
If you’re tired, you can take a break. I wouldn’t mind at all.
I’m not tired.
I’m actually happy that the outcome is worth the effort.
Are you happy with it, Boss?
I think so.
But there’re things that need to be improved for next time.
That answer sounds so you, Boss.
You did a great job today.
Yes?
Chonlada,
well done.
A girl like you who doesn’t know how to work should better keep your mouth shut.
At first, when Boss told me you’d be my assistant;
to be honest, I had so many doubts in mind.
Boss doesn’t usually let anyone work closely with her.
But why is it that she easily agreed and let you do it?
You’ve only been working here for a few weeks and haven’t done anything much.
It might be too fast to expect a compliment from me.
I know.
Preem told me it took you almost a year to compliment her.
But for you, it’ll probably take years.
Or you’re just doing it to give yourself an excuse for not telling your brother about Chef Ian…
because your boss didn't do anything wrong,
and because you’re falling into your own trap.
I just gave you a compliment.
Why are you crying?
I don’t have a handkerchief.
Wipe your tears on my shirt instead then.
Are you okay?
You were just crying earlier but now you’re laughing.
Thank you…for the answer you gave me that day.
What day?
That day when you told me to choose between the preferred suit or the right suit.
You made me realise something and decided to go for that answer.
What answer?
At first, I was too scared to choose.
But then your words of advice helped me make up my mind.
And I sure made the right choice.
Thank you.
Oh, there they are!
What is it, Dad?
Can I borrow your assistant for a while?
Come, Lada.
What for, Dad?
Probably to pair her up with someone.
Let’s go, Lada.
Why are you blocking me?
I’m only borrowing her for a few minutes.
It won’t be long.
Long or not, you can’t take her anyway.
As her boss,
I can’t allow her to do anything nonsense other than work.
Let’s go.
Boss!
We have a problem.
What happened?
Those guests who ate Chef Ian’s food.
They suddenly vomited and got an upset stomach.
Ouch!
Uncle! What’s wrong?
Uncle!
Dad! Dad.
Are you all right?
- Uncle.
- Are you okay?
Please have a seat first.
Oh, that’s all right.
How’s he doing?
Just a moment please.
Did you get some sleep?
Looks like you didn’t get any sleep either.
Miss Preem told me you were at the hospital all night,
following up on every guest’s condition.
So, did you get any sleep?
Don’t worry, it’s my job anyway.
How is Big Boss doing?
Hello.
I’m so sorry.
Sorry about what?
Hello?
It was you, wasn’t it?
Hold on, Lada. What are you talking about?
Poisoning the food at the event.
You did it, didn’t you?
Lada, it was you who did that.
Impossible. I already threw it away.
So, you betrayed me?
You refused to help our family’s hotel?
I’m so sorry.
But I just couldn’t do it.
It wasn’t right, Pat. You’re not playing it fair.
If you didn’t do it, then it was probably someone else.
Someone else? You also sent someone to work here apart from me?
Don’t let me down again.
Because the Watin Group won’t be losing only their name next time.
I’ll make them lose something else too.
Pat!
Boss trusted me to take care of this event.
But I failed to protect our hotel’s guests and reputation.
I’m really sorry.
Nam said the police have already looked into it.
The cause of food poisoning mainly comes from the ice being contaminated.
It’s not your fault, Lada.
You don’t have to apologise.
But if I had been more careful, something terrible like this wouldn’t have happened.
Do you know what I had to go through for the Watin Group to come this far?
It wasn’t easy at all. I’ve met all kinds of people.
And for someone like you, I can see through it all.
I have absolutely no doubt that you've done all you can to protect us, the Watin Group.
If you really feel guilty, you should go home and rest.
I’m giving you a day off.
Don’t come to work today.
Boss.
All the guests who attended the event are safe now.
And I still have a lot more work for you to do.
If my assistant gets so stressed out and falls sick, how do you expect me to focus on work then?
Just admit you’re worried about her.
Stop using work as an excuse.
Dad.
Jimlim, is Fah here yet?
I’ll get her for you, sir.
Oh, there she is.
The doctor is here, Uncle.
Hello, Uncle. How are you feeling?
Much better.
This is Trai. He’s the son of Chaiyuth,
the doctor who used to take care of me.
Trai, this is Lada, the girl I said I’d like to introduce to you last night.
Very nice to meet you, Miss Chonlada.
Finally, you two met.
Boss, your dad might feel crossed if you suddenly leave like this.
Let him be. It’s better than having you do something you don’t want to.
Or are you afraid you’ll be in trouble?
No, it’s not like that.
I just don’t want you and Big Boss to have a quarrel.
Hurry up and get in the car. Dad and I usually argue all the time.
But…
Or do you still want to talk to Trai?
Should I take you back inside?
What does he have to do with this?
If not, then get in the car. I’ll drop you off at the condo.
It’s okay, I can go back myself.
Please go get some rest, Boss.
Okay, fine! I get it.
If I let you go back alone, do you think I’ll be able to sleep?
I’ll drive you home.
I think she’s getting serious this time.
Yeah, it's all up to Lada now.
Yes?
How did you know?
What are you doing?
Pat! Pat!
Is there something wrong?
Nothing. Let’s go.
Hey, wrong building. That way.
It’s nothing. Let’s go.
Look out, Boss!
Are you okay?
Are you all right, Chonlada?
We’re…we’re here?
You don’t have to walk me to my room.
I can go up there myself.
Thank you for driving me.
Wait, Chonlada.
Boss, why did you get out?
Well, I…
Look out!
Pizza?
Are you okay?
What’s wrong?
I’m sorry. I told you to stay in the car.
Please leave now, Boss. Go home. Go.
Hold on!
I’m hungry.
Boss, can you wait here first?
Why? Is your room untidy?
No, it’s not. I just need to take care of something first.
Please wait a second.
It’s done.
Please come in.
All I have now is instant noodles.
They’re full of sodium so I’m not sure if you can eat them.
Of course, I can.
Which flavour do you want?
I have plenty for you to choose from.
Which one do you like?
All of them.
Otherwise, I wouldn’t have bought so many.
Then, what flavour do you want to eat now?
How about Miso Ramen? It’s not spicy. You can surely have it.
How hungry are you?
Can you wait? I’m going to make one at a time.
Let’s make two at once.
Then we can share.
I guess food can really help.
Yes?
What did you say?
You’ve been acting quite weird since downstairs.
Are you all right?
I’m just still worried about what happened this morning.
I’m worried Chef Ian might be upset.
I wonder who wouldn’t be.
All the guests at the event had an upset stomach.
They probably believe it’s because of Chef Ian’s food.
Will Chef Ian still agree to work with us then?
She actually wanted to cancel it at first.
What happened earlier has somehow ruined her reputation and discredited her.
But I already talked to her this morning.
Our hotel will arrange a press conference…
and take sole responsibility for everything.
We’ll also tell the press that it’s all our fault.
So the actual cause doesn’t come from the ice but the food?
Not the food.
But from the substance contaminated in the food.
Did someone poison the food?
Do you know who did it?
After checking the CCTV, some of our staff could be on a suspect list.
But it’d take some time to investigate and confirm who actually did it,
what they did it for, or who ordered them to do it.
Does it feel better?
It’s all right. I’m used to it. I often cook at home.
Why don’t you go and sit on the couch first?
I’ll bring it to you once it’s done.
It’s okay. Let me help you with it.
No need. You’re the guest, Boss. Let me take care of you.
Geez, that hurts.
Let me help.
It’s okay. Let me do it.
It’s okay.
Give it to me.
I’ll get a new one for you.
Here you go.
Just a second, Boss.
Now, we can eat while looking at the stars. Quite a happy meal, isn’t it?
By the way, there are still some left if you want more. I made loads of them.
Why are you sitting on the floor, Boss?
But you’re also not sitting on a couch.
I’m comfier this way.
I like it here too.
Now I know why you and Big Boss often argue.
It’s because you’re so stubborn like a mule.
I probably got it from you.
Are you saying I’m stubborn?
This noodle is quite good.
That means you’re opening up for a plain and useless thing.
It’s because you made them.
Oh, I…I forgot to give you something to drink.
I’ll get some water for you.
I’m sorry, Boss! I didn’t mean it!
I’m so sorry, Boss!
Oh my gosh, I’m sorry.
I’m so sorry.
I’m sorry.
Why don’t you get some cloth to wipe it instead, Chonlada?
Okay.
Nam!
Why are you looking so pretty today?
But this wasn’t what you were wearing when you left home.
They’re Chonlada’s.
Huh?
Hang on.
It’s not what I think it is, is it?
I had a little accident.
What happened?
I was eating noodles and spilled them on my shirt.
Where did you eat them?
And why do you have to change into her clothes?
Her room.
Her room?
Don’t imagine things.
Nothing happened.
Okay, that’s good then.
This means I can still pair Lada up with Trai.
It’s nothing for now. But there might be something in the future.
What was that again?
Tell Dad to tell that doctor Trai…
that from now on, Chonlada won’t have time for anyone.
Oooh, really?
♫ You’re the one that change my life ♫
♫ Make me feel more important than anyone♫
Give me five!
♫ Thank you so much♫
♫ For making my life meaningful♫
♫ How lucky I am to have you♫
Good morning.
Chonlada.
Boss.
When did you get here?
I’ve been waiting here for a while.
But you were too busy with your phone.
And didn’t look up at all.
Why would you want to see me, Boss?
I need to talk to you.
About what?
Are you looking for someone?
No. So, what do you want to talk to me about?
Let’s talk in the car.
Yes?
Get in the car.
Are you afraid someone might follow?
You keep looking around nervously.
It’s nothing. So, why do you want to talk to me?
Eat something first.
They’re from my dad.
Thank you.
Is it not good?
If you bought it, please tell the shop to improve their sauce a little.
I’ll let them know.
But they seem to put their heart into making it.
Yesterday, when you told me about,
our staff being interrogated,
can you tell me who they are?
I’m afraid I can’t.
Why?
It’s still under investigation.
We still can’t confirm who actually did it.
If I give you the names but it turns out they didn’t do it, those people might have a hard time working here after that.
Does that mean those who are being interrogated are our hotel’s employees?
Why would you want to know?
I’m just curious.
So, what is it that you want to talk to me about?
- Well, I…
- Sis!
Miss you so much!
Fai, how did you get here?
I came to Chumphon yesterday to take care of something.
And I thought maybe I should stop by to see you before I go home.
You and Lom are the same.
Never told me beforehand.
Unlike your big sister. Din always let me know before she’d come.
There you go again.
This is Miss Chonlada.
This is Atchima, my little sister.
Miss Chonlada?
Is she the girl Lom said is your girlfriend?
We’re just colleagues.
Nothing more than that.
About that work you want me to do, I’ll get it done as soon as possible.
What?
Pat, where are you?
I’m exactly where I should be.
Why do you sound so serious?
That’s because I couldn’t get a hold of you.
So, you just told everyone you and your boss are only colleagues?
Do you think that’d help?
You’re wondering which one is the mole, aren’t you?
Pat, I’m begging you.
You’re smart and talented. That’s why you’re able to look after our hotel and make it this far.
Please don’t stoop so low.
Hearing you said that, I’m completely convinced that your lady boss is so important to you.
It’s not what you think.
Boss and I are…
What? If you and Miss Chonlada are just colleagues,
does that mean Lom only imagined it?
You know what she’s like. Always imagine things and overreact.
But she looks so hurt and frustrated this time.
She even flew all the way there just to vent it out on me.
That’s why I have to come here for once to see the face of a girl who could make Lom so desperate like that.
But judging from your reaction…You too, right?
Maybe Lom isn’t the only one who feels it.
You’ve just arrived. Why don’t you get some rest first?
You feel it too, don’t you?
I already told you. Chonlada and I are just colleagues.
What do you want me to feel about her?
I don’t know about Miss Chonlada, but for you…
If you don’t feel anything for her, why did you tell Lom that she can’t pursue Miss Chonlada?
Do you have a secret crush on her?
If you don’t want to go back to your room, you can hang around here
I have work to do.
Not so fast.
Ouch!
Aww, did you just blush?
Din, if you’re not busy, find some time to come to Hua Hin with Boss Rose.
You should be able to see the person who can make our Nam divorce with her work.
I’m serious. Come and see it for yourself.
[Boss]
Hello?
Is there something you want to talk to me, Boss?
Are you free this evening after work?
I’d like to take you to try out the food at this restaurant.
I’m not free.
What about tomorrow?
Tomorrow too.
Are you free any day this week?
I’m a little tied up these days.
I’m sorry, Boss.
Hold on.
Have I done anything to upset you?
No.
If that’s all, I’m afraid I have to leave. Miss Preem has asked me to take care of something.
Sis.
You’re looking for me?
Shhh! Keep it down.
What is it?
Promise me first, that you won’t tell anyone about it.
Do you want me to sign an NDA too?
I’m serious.
I know, your face just says it all.
It’s about Miss Chonlada, isn’t it?
I just don’t understand. She suddenly acts like she’s mad at me.
But when I asked her what’s wrong or if she has any problem, she kept denying it.
What’s wrong with her, Fah?
I’m totally lost here.
You seem to care about her a lot.
I just don’t want to have problems with my colleagues.
If we’re on bad terms, we’ll surely have a hard time working together.
I don’t want to wait until it’s too late.
She didn’t tell me anything about taking leaves.
She only wrote ‘for personal matters’ on the leave letter.
Usually, she’d always let me know in clear detail where she’d go or what she’d do.
Aww, sis. That’s nothing.
All you have to do is give her a call and ask.
What if she doesn’t tell me?
That’s not a problem either.
You have an idea?
Lada, why didn’t you tell me you’d come home, sweetie?
Mum, has Pat been home lately?
Your dad is also looking for him.
I heard the hotel is having a lot of problems.
No one can get a hold of him.
Your dad told Wat to get Pat to come in for a talk tomorrow.
What does Dad want to talk to him about?
Pat’s phone is off.
Loser.
If that brat wants to keep avoiding me like this…
Wat, just do as I said.
But Dad, are you sure?
Why on earth should I keep it then?
The more we persist, the more money we’d lose.
If he can’t manage just a small hotel branch and even loses to Adisorn’s daughter,
then shut it down and sell the whole thing off!
Do you really have to do that, Dad?
If Pat finds out, he might…
I’m doing this because I want to teach him that being my son means you must always win.
There’s no place for losing.
Especially when he’s losing to a girl like Adisorn’s daughter.
If he still wants to be in a hotel business,
let him beg for a job from that brat’s daughter then.
If Pat knows that Dad’s going to sell it off,
he would never let that happen.
But Dad already made up his mind.
No one can do anything now.
Not really. Pat clearly takes after his father.
They’d rather die than losing their faces.
And now, Pat is like someone who’s striving for his last breath.
I’m sure he’d do anything to keep his hotel going.
Listen,
if you still want more after finishing this one, maybe we should go out for a drink tonight.
Not funny.
Hey, I’m serious.
If staying with the Watin Group makes you so stressed like this,
since your dad is going to sell off your brother’s hotel anyway;
why don’t you just back off?
I can’t.
You’re not falling into your own trap, are you?
It doesn’t matter how I feel.
The point is I can’t leave Boss right now.
Why?
Is there anything you still haven’t told me, Lada?
Hey, Lada.
This one is important. I have to take it.
But I’ll be back to get an answer from you.
You’d better have it ready. I’ll be right back.
Hello, Boss.
How have you been?
I’m good.
[Boss]
[Chonlada]
The work won’t get itself done without putting in any effort
The same also goes with love.
What are you doing here, Dad?
You’ve been looking so depressed for many days now.
At first, I thought I would leave you alone.
But so far, I don’t think anything good will come out of it.
I’m only stressing about work, not about Chonlada.
I haven’t mentioned anything about Lada yet.
Don’t get so defensive.
Geez, Dad!
Fine, if you insist that I should stay out of this…I’ll do that.
Wait, Dad.
I…I just feel that Chonlada is trying to avoid me.
So, do you want me to help or not?
So, for last Monday and Tuesday?
Okay, I’ll bring them down to you in a minute.
Miss Preem, these are documents from the accounting department that you’ve asked me to get from them.
Can you give them to Boss for me?
Can you give them to Boss for me? I have to go talk to Miss Wadee first.
Why don’t you give them to Boss yourself?
I’ll go get Miss Wadee for you.
That’s all right. I’ll be right back. Take care of it for me.
Boss!
What are you doing?
Don’t move.
Why didn’t you answer my call?
I left my phone on the table.
Miss Preem already told me.
That’s why I’ve got this for you.
You should wear it.
It’ll come in handy in case of an emergency or when you forget your phone.
The watch will notify you when there’s an incoming call.
Do you perhaps have any problem with me, Chonlada?
No, Boss.
Liar.
I’m not lying.
I really don’t have any problem with you.
Or do you want me to say otherwise?
Your heart rate is too high.
You want me to put this on so that you can check if I’m lying?
Then don’t take it off if you have nothing to hide.
Or are you afraid?
I’m not. I don’t want to put it on because I think it’s nonsense.
It might look nonsense to you.
But to me, to have someone who seems close suddenly turns estranged and keeps avoiding me, it matters a lot.
You probably imagine it, Boss.
We have to work together every day, there’s no way I’d be able to avoid you.
Now, if you’ll excuse me.
If you insist I imagine it,
then can we go out and have dinner together tonight?
If you don’t like a fancy restaurant, we can have some noodles at the stall near your condo.
I’m afraid I’ll have to turn down the offer.
I already have another plan.
See? I’m not lying.
Please excuse me, Boss.
[Boss Adisorn]
If you’re staying late, I can stay and help.
No need. You can go home.
I think I’ll sleep here tonight…
since I got turned down anyway.
Your appointment got cancelled?
But it’s not on your schedule, Boss.
Never mind.
It’s a last-minute one.
Yes, Boss.
By the way, Big Boss just called and said that you didn’t pick up his call.
Tell him I’m busy.
I have to get some work done.
I told him exactly that.
But he said there’ll be an important guest coming for dinner at your place tonight.
And if you want to know who it is, you should take a look at his message.
Is it urgent?
No, Boss.
I’ll do it tomorrow then.
Shut down the air-con for me.
See you tomorrow.
[Next Episode]
Excuse me?
[Pheempat]: The Watin Group is going to have a private event for a big group of customers.
It must be ruined, Lada.
I will wreck it!
Chonlada! Chonlada!
Please don’t do this, Boss.
You have no idea how scared I am.
[Nam]: I don’t know what it is that you fear.
But if you’re worried about me,
then don’t leave me.
[Lada]: I’m going to tell Miss Apo everything and end this!
Go on, I also want to know…
what she’d say when she finds out you’re my sister.
[Lada]: What you want between us is impossible.
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my sight♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
♫Honestly, I can’t help but still doubt it♫
♫Are you really that person my heart has been looking for?♫
♫ Is this love? Is that what they call it?♫
♫ When my heart starts to waver♫
♫ Like a stream of water slowly pouring over my heart♫
♫ From dusk till dawn, you’re never far from my thought♫
♫ Or is this love? Are you that someone...♫
♫ ...who’s destined to be with me?♫
♫ Is this really happening ? I really want to know ♫
♫‘Cos you now hold a special place in my heart♫
[Waves of Deception]